Tang Phuoc Quang

Software Engineer quanggtangg@gmail.com · (+84) 39 654 6280

SUMMARY

Experienced software engineer with around three years of expertise in front-end development using React and its ecosystem. I've had the opportunity to work on a variety of projects in e-commerce, healthcare, and AI recently. I have a strong desire to seek new knowledge to grow my skills and experience as well as join the growth of the organization.

SKILLS

React / Next, typescript Redux, tailwind Mui, chakra, shadon, ... Node / Express Prisma, Mongodb And basic knowledge in some other tools: Figma, Linux, Docker, ...

WORK EXPERIENCE

Freelance May 2023 - Sep 2023

Persona Al

staging.getpersona.ai

An Al assistant project - simplify daily life tasks by providing chatbot coaches for every aspect, from cooking to making reservations, buying groceries, travel booking, and many more.

- As the first engineer, my duties were designing and structuring the project and joining in hiring teammates.
- I used Nextjs as a full-stack app along with tailwindcss, shaden on front-end, prisma and mongodb in the backend. Typescript, eslint and a bunch of lint tools to maintain coding style and convention.
- Researched and implemented third-party services like Openai, elevenlabs, Twilio, ... to process languages, support API and multi-channels.
- Received requirements from the CEO, collaborated along with my senior, built up the project within 2 months, and successfully raised from venture capital.

ITdeck

A writing supporter project using APIs powered by Writesonic AI, easily generates a text, an email, or the whole essay with some keyword input.

Worked directly with the manager and designer, received requirements, and converted the design to an interactive web app. Collaborate with my back-end dude to develop and release the features on time.

Now in progress	looking for investment.	

Front-end developer at Buymed | thuocsi.vn

June 2022 - April 2023

Circa.vn

A B2C medicine e-commerce project, re-use available resources of thuocsi.vn to develop a solution for customers to buy and receive medicine from everywhere in Vietnam effortlessly.

- Designing and structuring front-end source base using nextjs and typescript.
- Collaborated with designers and the back-end team to continuously deliver the features.
- Participating in peer code review to obtain the highest quality code possible.
- Ensure consistency of the code among teammates by applying a bunch of lint tools.
- Support BA in manually testing and fixing my own bugs

POS

pos.circa.vn

An in-house project provided to medicine store owners to manage supplies, bills and prescriptions.

The first time I had the privilege to start the project from scratch.

- Set up front-end source base with Next, typescript, tailwind, and material-ui.
- Research and implement new libraries for the project.
- Received requirements directly from manager, collaborated with designer and back-end team to deliver the product.
- After the team had more members, I was moved to work on a whole new project circa.vn

Front-end developer at Goalist Co.,Ltd.

July 2021 - Feb 2022

Jopus connecter

connecter.jopus.net

A recruitment platform service specialized for foreigners looking for work in Japan.

- Receive the design, revamping the UI to significantly improve user experience.
- Collaborate with Japan's design team for quality checks and bug fixes.
- Technologies: HTML, SASS, JS

Casting Road

hr-visual.jp

A B2B data visualization platform provides insight look by combining data from other organizations in the HR industry.

- Assisting the senior developers in coding and contributing to fixing bugs.
- Implement socket on front end to receive events passively.
- Implement new features following design and requirements.
- Technologies: nextjs, typescript, spring, mysql, hibernate, ...

Hrog

hrog.co.jp

A CMS platform provided a project showcase for Hrog and Goalist partners.

My main work was about managing the contents, converting the document to the content on the UI using HTML, CSS, and Gohugo

Intern Full-stack developer at Save money Corporation

May 2020 - May 2021

Insurwin

A B2C platform simplifies the process of buying any type of insurance from multiple providers just by providing some basic information.

- Assisting the senior developers in creating new features, fixing bugs, and accidentally creating new bugs sometimes.
- Joined in daily scrum meetings and planning.
- Developing dynamic UI on the frontend and CRUD API in the backend with REST and Graphql.
- Performed code review, and worked closely with team members to ensure consistency with code standards.

EDUCATION & CERTIFICATIONS

Cybersoft Academy Dec 2019 - April 2020

Studied front-end development.

Cao Thang Technical College Sep 2018 - Nov 2019

Studied front-end development.

REFERENCES

Huynh Cong Van Front-end team leader at PersonaAl. (+84) 97 6342 208 congvan203@gmail.com

Joined me on the journey to develop getpersona.ai.

Having a chance to work with him is my honor, been through a lot of struggles and misunderstandings, and what I got from him was a considerable amount of knowledge in both technical and working styles that I feel like I am going to need a lot of time to understand without him.